Making such a fuss here.
Since you've let go,
I'll be leaving now.
Y-You may rise.
Wen Lingli.
What's wrong?
I sprained my ankle.
Can't you move it?
I can't.
Is it swollen?
Wait a minute.
It might be a sprained ankle.
Yin Zixi, stop right there.
What's going on?
Mr. Wang.
Don't just look, help out!
I'll carry her.
Why is this kid
so heavy?
Mr. Wang,
if there's nothing else,
I'll get going.
Wait.
Come back.
Zixi,
you're usually quite quiet
in class.
Why did you
get into a fight with your classmate today?
This
is a bit hard to explain.
What's so hard to explain?
Mr. Wang,
am I really your student?
How come I don't remember
ever taking your class before?
Did the fight mess with your head?
I am
your homeroom teacher,
Mr. Wang.
Look for yourself.
Class 1, Grade 2016, Department of Journalism.
Yin Zixi,
is that you?
Prajna Paramita.
Avada Kedavra.
Diary of mysterious power,
Xiaoxi, who once made a pact with you,
commands you to
release the seal.
Release.
Oh.
What am I doing?
My 3 million fans
are still waiting for me to log in.
How on earth can I go back?
Where do you want to go back to?
2024, of course.
Then you need to recite
Sailor Moon's catchphrase.
The champion of love and justice.
In the name of the moon, I'll punish you!
Goodbye, pretty girl.
Yin Zixi, where are you going?
You know me?
Of course.
I am your best friend on planet M1703,
Yang Qian.
Ha.
This is planet M1703.
Class 1, Journalism Department, Grade 2016.
Yin Zixi.
This is really me.
You bought so much.
I bought it with my mom.
She recently got obsessed with watching live streams.
A man selling lipsticks.
Oh my god, buy it.
You watch live streams too?
At least I have 3 million followers.
Three million followers?
I remember.
He seems to only have tens of thousands of followers.
That's now.
He suddenly reached three million followers.
Gaining followers isn't that easy.
From now on...
If it were me...
Is this my destiny?
The top livestreamer,
Yin Zixi.
I need to turn over a new leaf
and start fresh.
Please enjoy.
Hey, Brother Liang Chen,
is your selection confirmed this time?
Yes.
But what's going on with your side?
I might have gone a bit too far this time.
Too far?
It's simply outrageous.
In the entire competition,
you are actually the only girl.
Well, I just
approached those girls
for a little chat, that's all.
Yeah.
But the other girls are all too scared to participate.
What?
Is it my fault that they are cowards?
No.
Oh, I have a good idea.
We can find some
plain girls to participate.
It won't affect your chances,
and the teacher won't suspect anything.
Plain?
I have someone in mind.
Who?
The first one,
Yin Zixi.
Do you want to keep your current length
or try a shorter style?
I want the current length.
How about this.
A high ponytail makes you look more elegant.
This Yin Zixi
is in our class.
The one who always wears her high school uniform
and looks so tacky.
She gave me a hard time before,
so it's a good chance to let her make a fool of herself on stage.
Done writing.
Can they all come?
When I handle things,
you don't need to worry.
Go ahead.
Keep up the good work.
I'm leaving.
Yang Qian.
Huh? Where is everyone?
I went home today.
There's an invitation for you on the desk.
Dear Yin Zixi,
Your temperament and image
have impressed the Xihai University Endorsement Preparatory Committee.
We hereby invite you
to participate in tomorrow's selection event.
What the hell?
I'm not participating.
What's wrong with this diary again?
The preparatory committee sent me an invitation.
I don't know how they found me,
but I decided to give it a try.
What's going on?
Why are there so few people?
Hello.
Hi beautiful,
who are you?
I'm Yin Zixi.
The college entrance exam is like thousands of troops
crossing a single-log bridge.
We worked so hard
to get into college.
I didn't expect her to join too.
Finally, someone decent.
Mr. Wang,
is this your student?
It's a pity the speech was average.
And the lines weren't well-memorized.
It is a bit of a shame.
From the first day of college,
students must set clear goals.
I hope later on stage,
this diary
won't cause any more trouble.
Guided by the right goals,
we can start a brand new voyage.
That concludes my speech.
Thank you, professors.
Next.
Yin Zixi.
Hello, professors.
I am from the 2016 Journalism Class 1,
Yin Zixi.
So you are Yin Zixi.
Please begin.
Am I going to be dragged on stage
to make a fool of myself again?
For the campus ambassador selection,
winners will receive
a school-sponsored startup fund
and on-campus entrepreneurial support.
Returning to campus,
I can't help but
think about
my days as a student.
I wonder if you've ever thought about
what you'll be like in seven years.
Where will you be?
What will you be doing?
Sigh.
This is a headache.
Ah.
Wen Lingli's is over.
It's over.
Boss, why are you here?
We cannot be certain of
our future.
The one on the stage.
Who is it?
Um, Yin Zixi.
Wen Lingli has finally met her match.
But precisely because
there are so many uncertainties,
all of this
is waiting for us to figure out.
Assistant Casting Director Xi Chongjingü
Props Assistant Li Kunxiao
Transport Yi Mingle
Yitong